Guide to the Arthur Peterson papers,1920-1976
Peterson, Arthur papers, 1920-1976
- Uihlein Properties (Box 10, Folder 48)
- United Fund (Box 10, Folder 49)
- University Theater (Latin-American Tour) (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Vegetable Crops (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Vocational Agriculture Teacher Training Program (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Warm Water Fisheries (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Water Resources Center (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Water Resources Center (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Water Resources Center (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Wheat Acreage (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Willard Straight Hall (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Workmen's Compensation (Box 11, Folder 4)
- WVBR (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Cornell Research Foundation (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Cornell Research Foundation (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Federal Research Funds (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Federal Research Funds (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Federal Research Funds (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Cornell Research Park (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Cornell Retirement Plan (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Cornell Retirement Plan (Box 11, Folder 13)
- N.Y.S. Employee Retirement System (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Cornell Research (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Dept. of Audit and Control (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Dept. of Agriculture and Markets (Box 11, Folder 17)
- State Budget Office (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Civil Service (Box 11, Folder 19)
- State Education Department (Box 11, Folder 20)
- State Education Department (Box 11, Folder 21)
- State University of New York - General (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Public Work - Division of Contracts (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Charles H. Foster (Box 11, Folder 24)
- State University of New York - General (Box 11, Folder 25)
- State University of New York - General (Box 11, Folder 26)
- State University of New York - General (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Cornell Computer Center (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Cornell Computer Center (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Cornell Computer Center (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Geneva Experiment Station (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Geneva Experiment Station (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Cornell Insurance Plans (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Cornell Insurance Plans (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Cornell Insurance Plans (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Liberian Contract (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Liberian Contract (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Legislature Bills (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Legislature Bills (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Letter Book #1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Liberia Survey Vouchers (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Survey Liberian Project (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Survey Liberian Project (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Letter Book, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Letter Book, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Agriculture, 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Agriculture, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Administrative Staff Meetings, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Geveva Experiment Station (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Geveva Experiment Station (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Agriculture (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Agriculture (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Job Orders, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Job Orders, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Job Orders, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Job Orders, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Veterinary College (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Veterinary College (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Veterinary College (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Personnel (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Personnel (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Personnel (Box 13, Folder 10)
- President Perkins 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- President Perkins, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Machine Records Division (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Machine Records Division (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Machine Records (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Machine Records Division Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- College of Home Economics (Box 13, Folder 17)
- College of Engineering (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Statler Financial Statements (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Statler Financial Statements (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Statler Financial Statements (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Contract College at Cornell - Monthly Balance Sheets (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Data Processing Center - Hotels (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Allegeny Co. Extension Service -, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Madison Co. Extension (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Madison Co. Extension (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Extension Division (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Extension Division (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Indonesia Project Report - University of Kentucky (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Bailey Hall Organ (Box 14, Folder 9)
- I. & L. R. School - Long Range Planning, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Group Life & Accidental (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Accounting Dept. (endowed) (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Arecibo (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Auditor (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Bailey Hortorium (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Biology (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Busses Parking (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Civil Defense (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Cohn Farm (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Conservation (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Cornellian, College Fleet, & Control Data (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Cornell Policies (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Cornell Residential Club (Box 14, Folder 23)
- European Productivity Agency (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Extension (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Extension Development in N. Y. City (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Fallout Shelters (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Filter Plant (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Finch-Pruyn-Cooperative Experimental Forest (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Ford Foundation - Int'l. Studies Center (Box 14, Folder 30)
- General, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Group Homes (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Personnel (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Safety (Box 14, Folder 34)
- State Dormitory Authority (Box 14, Folder 35)
- State Dormitory Authority (Box 14, Folder 36)
- State Dormitory Authority (Box 14, Folder 37)
- State Dormitory Authority (Box 14, Folder 38)
- WHCU (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Ford Foundation Grants (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Foreign Grad. Students in Agriculture (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Foreign Visitors (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Forestry Research (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Fulbright-Hayes Act (Box 15, Folder 6)
- General Extension (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Ghana (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Ghana (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Glee Club - Far East Tour (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Golden Nematode (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Golden Nematode (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Graduate School (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Grants (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Haskins & Sells (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Heller House (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Hockey Squad (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Home Economics (Box 15, Folder 18)
- ID Cards (Box 15, Folder 19)
- International (Box 15, Folder 20)
- International (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Property Map - Ithaca Airport (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Ithaca Staff Purchases (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Labor Legislation (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Department of Labor Recommendations (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Land Grant Centennial (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Latin American Year (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Library (Box 15, Folder 28)
- L. I. Land Purchases (Box 15, Folder 29)
- L. I. Vegetable Research Farm (Box 15, Folder 30)
- McDonald Farm (Box 15, Folder 31)
- McDonald Farm (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Materials Science Center (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Caldwell Hall (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Veterinary College (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Veterinary College (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Veterinary College (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Drill Hall (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Comstock Hall (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Comstock Hall (Box 15, Folder 41)
- James Law hall (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Fernow Hall (Box 15, Folder 43)
- VanRensselaer Hall (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Barton Hall (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Rice Hall (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Snyder Hall (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Rose Garden File (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Rose Garden File (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Landscaping (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Grounds Lighting (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Greenhouses (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Engineering Building (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Rehabilitation due to Library Shift (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Gas & Electric Service (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Steam Lines & Tunnels (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Drainage & Irrigation (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Refrigeration Systems (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Farm (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Rehabilitation Projects, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Barns & Small Animal Clinic (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Library Building (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Library Building (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Central Heating Plant - Geneva (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Central Heating Plant - Geneva (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Geneva Water System (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Pomology Storage Building (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Coping and Masonry Work (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Electrical Service (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Buildings (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Road Maintenance (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 25)